bankwindhoek.com.na 2013-07-30

# PrivacyPolicy

At Bank Windhoek we are 100% committed to ensure your privacy and as such we respect your need for appropriate protection and management of personally identifiable information that you share with us when accessing our website. Our privacy policy is specifically designed to respect and address your needs.

“Personally identifiable information” is all that information specific to you that you provide us over the Internet when accessing and making use of our website. Such information primarily includes personal data like your full name, personal telephone numbers (home/office/cellular) and your addresses (residential/postal/office). You will be required to disclose this kind of information when, for example, you apply for a new account online, or request information regarding our site via e-mail 

When will we ask you to furnish us with your personally identifiable information?

There are a number of instances where this kind of information will be required, for instance: 

  1. When you apply over the Internet for an account with us, we will collect personal information from you in order to process your application. We may retain this information to enable us to provide additional products and services, offered by our subsidiaries, that you might request. Our subsidiaries adhere to our privacy policy. 

  2. Should you, as a customer, make use of our electronic banking service this service records all your “online” sessions, including the transactions you authorise and transact online. This data enables us to process and confirm your transactions. 

  3. When you communicate with us via e-mail, we retain the content of your e-mail, together with your e-mail address particulars, and our response thereto. This is done so that we may appropriately deal with any follow-up questions you may have. This data is also used to determine how efficiently and effectively we address your concerns. 

### How does Bank Windhoek use your personally identifiable information? 

Because we are committed to respecting your privacy, Bank Windhoek will only use your personally identifiable information in the normal course of our business to provide you with the products and services you have requested. In order to combat incidents of fraud, your personal identifiable information will also be used to positively identify you when you contact us. 

It will also enable us to maintain contact with you and give us the opportunity to inform you about any updates on services and products that we believe may be of importance or interest to you. It's just another way we try to continually meet your expectations of us as a bank and ensure that together we do better by “adding value to you”. 

### Will Bank Windhoek divulge your personally identifiable information to other persons? 

Due to our commitment to uphold your privacy, Bank Windhoek does not and will not sell, trade, provide or make available your personally identifiable information to third parties for independent use. We may, however, share your personally identifiable information with our subsidiaries or other business partners if that information is required to provide the product or service you have requested. Should we do so, we shall ensure that our subsidiaries and business partners subscribe to and adhere to this privacy policy. 

Our website may contain links to or from other sites. While we try to link only to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy, we are not responsible for the content or the security or privacy practices employed by other sites. As such we recommend that you always read the privacy and security statements on such sites. 

### Bank Windhoek may release your personally identifiable information when: 

  1. we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to: 

    * comply with legal requirements as prescribed by legislation, the judiciary or any supervisory or regulatory authority; and/or 

    * enforce or apply the terms of use relating to our website; and/or 

    * protect the rights, property or safety of Bank Windhoek Limited, its other users, and the public. 
  2. we are instructed to do so by legislation, the judiciary or any supervisory or regulatory authority. 

### Can you confirm the correctness of your personally identifiable information that we collect? 

Yes, absolutely. In the event that you ever question or dispute the accuracy of your personally identifiable information held by us, please contact us as soon as possible. We will investigate your question and update our records as needed. 

To enable us to provide you with the best quality service, we kindly request that you keep your information as up-to-date as possible (by informing us of any changes to your personally identifiable information via e-mail). 

### How is your personally identifiable information protected? 

We are committed to providing secure online banking services using the Internet. As such, all interactions with our website are protected through encryption that complies with international standards. Encryption is used to protect the transmission of your personally identifiable information when completing online application forms. Our Internet servers are protected by firewalls and intrusion detection systems. Access to information on these servers is restricted to authorised personnel only. We have also employed the services of independent security experts to test and advise us on the security of our systems and are pleased to inform you that our systems' security complies with internationally acceptable standards. 

To ensure that you benefit from our security you should read the security tips we post on our website from time to time. 

### May Bank Windhoek update this privacy policy? 

We reserve the right to amend this privacy statement at any time. All amendments to this statement will be posted on the website. Unless otherwise stated, the current version of this statement shall supersede and replace all previous versions of the statement. 

### Who do you contact if you have questions about this privacy statement? 

If you have any questions about this privacy and security statement please e-mail us at: [info@bankwindhoek.com.na ](mailto:info@bankwindhoek.com.na)

Back to top
